portolawalk.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Portola Walk

Effective 11/1/2010

Olson Urban Housing, LLC, doing business as “The Olson Company”, and its subsidiaries and affiliated entities (“Olson”) provide the website arroyowalk.com (‘this Website”) to you (“You” or “Your”) subject to this Privacy Policy, its Terms and Conditions of Use (“Terms”), and its other policies.

This Privacy Policy describes the way in which Olson collects, uses, or shares any information You provide to Olson or information about Your use of this website. Olson may, and reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If You access this Website You are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time.

The most current version of this policy can be accessed at <http://www.olsonhomes.com/privacy>. By continuing to access or use this Website, You accept any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy.

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE**

### Personal Information Olson Collects

You may use this Website without creating an account. Even without an account, Olson collects information about your use of this Website. This may include information about any IP address used to access this Website and Your activity on this Website.

This Website may use “cookies.” Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to Your computers hard drive through Your Web browser (if You allow) that enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize Your browser and capture and remember certain information. This Website may use cookies to help Olson understand and save Your preferences for future visits, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that Olson can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. If You prefer, You can choose to have Your computer warn You each time a cookie is being sent, or You can choose to turn off all cookies via Your browser settings. Like most websites, if You turn Your cookies off, some of the Website services may not function properly.

”Personal Information” is information that is used by Olson to identify you individually, such as your name and address. Olson collects Personal Information that You voluntarily provide in creating an account at this Website or signing up for an interest list. This may include information such as Your name, address, email address, phone number, Your preferred contact, information about Your purchasing plans and home preferences, and information about how You became aware of Olson.

This Website and other internet and mobile device content and functionality provided by Olson may become available across multiple platforms and multiple types of devices. This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all internet-enabled devices and mobile devices, including, but not limited to “smartphones”. When connecting to this Website with such internet-enabled devices via a service provider which uniquely identifies your internet-enabled device, Olson may receive this identification and use it to offer additional services or functionality. Your use of certain services provided by Olson, including, but not limited to, the transmission of media message service (MMS) and short message service (SMS) or “text messages” to Olson, may require the collection of Your mobile phone number. Olson may associate that mobile phone number to the mobile device identification information. However, Olson will not use that phone number for telemarketing unless You have given Olson permission to do so.

### Use and Sharing of Personal Information

Olson may use Personal Information You provide to create and maintain Your account, to personalize Your experience, and to send periodic email communications relating to our services, such as purchase receipts, and account confirmations. Olson does not sell, exchange, transfer, or give this type of Personal Information to any other company without Your consent. If there is a material change in Olson’s use of Your Personal Information, Olson will obtain Your affirmative express consent if You are affected by such material change.

Olson may use Personal Information about Your use of this Website to improve its websites and services. Olson actively protects Your usage anonymity and does not distribute personally identifiable information about Your use of this Website to any third parties. Only aggregated use data that does not include personally identifiable information may be shared with third parties.

Olson reserves the right to disclose Personal Information to third parties if required to do so by law, or if Olson has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; (3) act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety.

Olson reserves the right to transfer Personal Information to any successor in interest to the Olson business.

### Children’s Privacy

This Website is directed to people who are at least 18 years old, and Olson does not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. If You are aware that Olson has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of 18, please alert Olson at [privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com](mailto:privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com) and the information will be removed from our system as soon as is reasonably possible. This policy regarding collection of data from children exceeds the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.

### Interest List

When You submit Your mailing address or email address to Olson through this Website, You may receive mail and emails that include Olson community news, updates, announcements, or information about particular communities of interest.

If at any time You would like to unsubscribe from receiving future mail or emails, please contact us at [privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com](mailto:privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com).

### Third Party Links

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information collected by Olson. This Website contains links to other websites that are not maintained or controlled by Olson, including social networking websites. A link to a third party website is not an endorsement of that website. Olson is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other Websites, and you are encouraged to, and accountable for, reviewing the privacy policy of such other websites before disclosing your personal information to such third parties. The fact that a link to a third party website exists on this Website does not mean that the third party site operates under the same or similar privacy practices as set forth in the Olson Privacy Policy.

Olson may include third party products or services on this Website. Individuals or companies outside of Olson, such as lenders or vendors of options for your home, are considered third parties. For example, if You use the “design your home” feature, this feature may be provided by a third party, “Options Online”. These third party websites have separate and independent terms and conditions for use and privacy policies. Olson has no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these third party websites.

### Contacting Olson

If You have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com](mailto:privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com) or mail at The Olson Company, 3010 Old Ranch Parkway, Suite 100, Seal Beach, California 90740.

### Opting Out

At any time you provide us with Personal Information, you have the opportunity to opt out of receiving further communications from us. To choose to opt out of receiving additional communications, or to unsubscribe from any specific email distribution, please email a request to [privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com](mailto:privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com). You may also stop email messages and other promotional communications by contacting our Webmaster at [privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com](mailto:privacyofficer@olsonhomes.com).
